Hey guys, it's officially less than 100 days till election day, so I just wanted to hop
on here to give a basic breakdown of what's at stake nationally this November.
2026 is a midterm election year, just meaning that it happens at the midway point of a president's
time in office, but it is super important because it holds the possibility of flipping
the majority party in Congress and in the Senate, which will set the tone for the remainder of a
president's time in office. Right now, Republicans hold the majority in both chambers of Congress,
which allows Trump and his administration to enact their agenda in a way that would not be
possible in a divided Congress. Because briefly stated, the party that holds the
majority shapes the direction of policy and holds control over the legislative
process. That's what makes midterm elections so important because during
midterm years all 435 seats of the House are up for re-election as well as the
regular one-third of Senate seats. What that means for this upcoming November is
Democrats have the chance to flip the House and the Senate which would make it
a lot more difficult for President Trump to make progress in his agenda. I
cannot overstate how important this is. We are in a pivotal time in history and
and flipping the House and the Senate is the most important thing we can do right now.
So please get out and vote. It really comes down to just upholding the principles of democracy,
so please do what you can, get involved, and like I already said, vote. That's all she wrote, bye guys!